{
    "subject": "Turai_Yar'Adua",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Umaru_Yar'Adua",
    "human_readable": "Turai Yar'Adua is married to Umaru Yar'Adua.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9765249490737915,
            "question": "To whom was Umaru Yar'Adua married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9764812588691711,
            "question": "Is Umaru Yar'Adua married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9699954390525818,
            "question": "Who is Turai Yar'Adua married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.944492757320404,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the marriage between Turai and Umaru Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9236440062522888,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Turai Yar'Adua and Umaru Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8478085994720459,
            "question": "Who is Turai Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5614355802536011,
            "question": "Can you provide more context about Turai and Umaru Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5167333483695984,
            "question": "Are there any other known facts about Turai Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5109896659851074,
            "question": "Is Umaru Yar'Adua a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06075410544872284,
            "question": "What is the significance of this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Turai Yar'Adua is married to Umaru Yar'Adua.",
            "html": "yago_14222_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Umaru Yar'Adua a public figure?",
            "html": "yago_14222_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other known facts about Turai Yar'Adua?",
            "html": "yago_14222_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more context about Turai and Umaru Yar'Adua?",
            "html": "yago_14222_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14222_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Turai Yar'Adua being married to Umaru Yar'Adua, with one of them specifically stating that they were married in 1975 and had seven children together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Turai Yar'Adua was married to Umaru Yar'Adua in 1975, and they had several children together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}